In the Matter of the PRR Merger with NYC Railroad Company Finance Dockett #'s 21989, 21990 Minutes 5557
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
In the Matter of the PRR Merger with NYC Railroad Company Finance Dockett #'s 21989, 21990 Minutes
1953-1963
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Interstate Commerce Commission (ICC)
NY Central Railroad Co. (NYC)
Pennsylvania Railroad Company (PRR)
5557
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Minutes (administrative records).
Photocopies of Stenographers Minutes, Incomplete
5664258
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, June 30, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 18, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Railroads--United States.; Railroads -- Mergers -- United States; New York Central Railroad Company; Pennsylvania Railroad.; United States. Interstate Commerce Commission
5664258
- Mediation Hearing RE: Railroad Wage Increases, Transcript Vol. 4, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  1/12
- Mediation Hearing RE: Railroad Wage Increases, Transcript Vol. 5, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  1/13
- Mediation Hearing RE: Railroad Wage Increases, Transcript Vol. 6, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  1/14
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.58, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  2/11
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.59, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  2/12
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.60, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  2/13
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.61, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  2/14
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.57, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  1/29
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol. 67, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  2/25
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol. 68, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  2/26
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol. 69, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  3/14
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.70, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  3/18
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.71, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  3/21
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.72, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  3/25
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.73, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  3/26
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.80, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  4/4
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, pp. 13,787-13,825, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.103, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  6/6
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.104, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  6/7
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.105, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  6/11
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.106, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  6/12
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.124, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  8/28
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.125, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  8/29
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.126, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  8/30
- Interstate Commerce Commission, Minutes RE: Penn Railroad Merger, Vol.127, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  10/1